Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
There's quite a competition
to launch their brand with us.
There are over 30 brands
that have sent us samples
just this week.
Many of these are dupes of what I saw
at the last Paris Fashion Week.
It had many innovative designs
so it looks like domestic brands
were heavily influenced.
If all they can do is copy
they can't work with Appello.
I'll look into just this brand.
All right.
Ms. Seo, please help out with that.
I'll join you right away
after figuring out the display.
Yes, I'll get the models ready
for the fitting.
- Okay, tell me when they're ready.
- Yes, sir.
This is just like you.
They aren't generic
and they carry their own identity.
That's how Appello started.
I was just collecting the clothes
I wanted to wear
which turned
into a tiny curated boutique.
And now, it's a platform
that carries hundreds of brands.
The pressure is different now.
Which you're carrying very well.
I'm in charge of the direction.
And if that direction is too skewed,
everyone who's following will fall.
Gosh, I know
that this is the time
to be more inclusive.
Yes, sir.
Yes, Mr. Kang. I'll do as you say
and pick up more mainstream designs.
EPISODE 2
Okay.
That bracelet on the man's hand.
- Take note of it.
- Yes.
Please get a tie
that's as bright as this one.
Right. Yes, sir.
Great work, everyone.
- Yes.
- Goodbye.
Text me the pictures we took today.
- Okay. Goodbye, Mr. Lee.
- Okay.
D.N.X! D.N.X! We love you, D.N.X!
You dropped this.
Right. Thank you.
Getting in?
What?
Oh, I am.
Don't be so nervous, Da-reum.
Try to act as naturally as possible.
NAM DA-REUM
- You must be one of the new hires.
- Sorry?
Yes.
Why weren't you there
at the welcome dinner?
I got a bit drunk last night
and went home early.
I see.
Anyway, it's nice to meet you,
Da-reum.
How do you know my name?
I look forward to working with you.
I'll do my best.
See you around.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
Goodbye.
My gosh.
My gosh!
I shook hands with Chan!
Great job on not getting too nervous.
Good one, Da-reum.
Goodbye.
WOLHWA SILVER WORKSHOP
Hey, what have you been
doing here for days?
Are you looking for a career change?
Should I do that?
D.N.X has disbanded
and not many would remember Lee Chan.
Hey.
I'm pretty good, aren't I?
You might as well
open a jewelry studio.
Hey, clean up everything
before I come back.
Okay?
- Hello.
By any chance, how much is this?
This is a DIY jewelry studio,
so we do not sell any items.
This was
one of our customers' designs.
This is the exact shape
that my all-time favorite celebrity
always draws
when he signs autographs.
Today's my birthday
so I want to buy it for myself
as a gift.
Can I please buy it?
I'm sorry.
But why don't you
try making it yourself?
I don't think
I can make it look exactly the same.
It's not as difficult as you think.
It's okay.
I understand. Thank you.
- Sure.
- Goodbye.
Okay. Goodbye.
WOLHWA SILVER WORKSHOP
It was you from back then.
- Great work today.
- Goodbye!
We've all done so well today!
See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow! Bye!
It looks like something great
must've happened to Da-reum.
Right? Our team has been
swamped with work lately.
Min-a, if it's okay with you
why don't we grab a glass of beer?
Gosh, beer?
No.
No?
You must be one of the new hires.
SUNGJU STATION
It's nice to meet you, Da-reum.
It was so great to meet you.
See you around.
See you!
Chan, let us meet again!
See you, Da-reum!
Bye!
Are you that happy?
Yes.
Someone might think
you just won the lottery.
It's her ultimate fan moment.
Fans who lived outside Seoul
can't go to music show recordings.
And at concerts, they look this small
so you can't even see their faces.
You've made it, Namda.
So? Would you like to smell my hand?
Jeez.
- No!
- Me too!
No, it's going to wear off.
I can't lose it!
Today is the first time
I've seen Chan in person.
I'll always celebrate this day.
You've always insisted
Chan gave you that necklace.
Do you finally admit
that you were overly hopeful?
But no one else
could have possibly made this.
Excuse me.
Happy birthday.
He definitely sounded like him too.
You're just misremembering
as a hopeful fan.
You think so?
Well, anyway.
I finally met him in person. My gosh!
I'm not dreaming, am I?
It hurts!
- It's not.
- It hurts.
APPELLO
This time, the overseas training
for outstanding employees
will be held
at the New York Fashion Week.
New York?
It sounds perfect.
You'll get to see a lot
and also have a mountain of work.
Overseas training
for outstanding employees?
It's a tradition of sorts
that Director Lee has made
since the foundation of Appello.
Once a year,
we pick out an outstanding employee
to do a project abroad.
Someone will be chosen
early next year.
Thank you. Come here, Min-a.
Does that mean
Director Lee will go on the trip too?
Of course.
He has never missed it once.
Who picks out
the outstanding employee?
Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kang?
AVOID MR. KANG
WORK HARD!
EMPLOYEE OVERSEAS TRAINING!
GET ON MR. KANG'S GOOD SIDE!
Well...
Is it okay
for my goal to change so drastically?
No, Da-reum.
You can do this.
First of all
I must figure out
what Mr. Kang is like.
Ms. Kim, this is for you.
Thank you.
Ms. Kim.
So what does Mr. Kang like?
Why are you asking about him?
I wasn't exactly
on my best behavior since day one
so I wanted to improve my reputation
and do my best at work.
Is that so?
Mr. Kang...
He only uses the brown capsules
for the coffee machine.
The brown ones?
Chocolate latte.
He has a sweet tooth,
unlike how he seems.
GUIDE TO WINNING CEO KANG HA-GI
OFFER HIM CHOCOLATE LATTE
Mr. Kang.
Would you like
a cup of sweet chocolate latte?
I made it just now.
No, I only drink one cup a day
because of my blood glucose level.
I've already had it,
so enjoy it for yourself.
Okay.
GUIDE TO WINNING CEO KANG HA-GI
CROSS OUT CHOCOLATE LATTE
I think he spends time on the rooftop
right after eating lunch.
He likes to spend at least 20 minutes
a day in the sun.
GUIDE TO WINNING CEO KANG HA-GI
BE SUNLIGHT BUDDIES
Oh, my.
I didn't know you came here too.
Great view, isn't it?
Yes.
I always get my share of sunlight
whenever I'm done with lunch.
People need sunlight to stay healthy.
Mr. Kang, people these days
are often low on vitamin D.
- Ms. Nam.
- Yes?
You're very distracting.
And don't stand in my view.
Right.
I'm sorry.
GUIDE TO WINNING CEO KANG HA-GI
CROSS OUT SUNLIGHT BUDDIES
Also, when you compliment him
on his style
he gets somewhat pleased.
GUIDE TO WINNING CEO KANG HA-GI
COMPLIMENT HIM
My gosh, Mr. Kang.
You look so cool
in that shirt and tie.
You could be a runway model.
I pulled an all-nighter,
so it's the same as yesterday.
Goodbye.
GUIDE TO WINNING CEO KANG HA-GI
CROSS OUT COMPLIMENTS
How come nothing is working?
You look so cool
in that shirt and tie.
You could be a runway model.
My gosh.
I looked into Ms. Nam
and she recently quit...
Just speak normally.
It's just the two of us here.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Nam recently resigned
from her job at SE Corporation.
I feel like she has a hidden agenda.
Maybe she's a honey trap
sent by Director Kim.
Honey trap?
I don't think so.
Exactly. It's nonsense.
How about a cuteness ploy?
Someone who traps you with cuteness.
That also doesn't make sense.
Is she here just to wreak havoc?
How do I get on Mr. Kang's good side?
- What's up?
- I mean
whenever I say something,
all he says is, "No, thanks."
There's no way to get through to him.
It's not like I'm into him.
I'm trying to be
the outstanding employee.
Maybe he thinks
you're hitting on him.
He just doesn't let anyone
get close to him.
Is that why he shuts you off?
No, he's like that
to everyone else too.
That's why the employees
nicknamed him Icy Kang.
He's that cold.
Hey, look at this.
Exclusive! Former K-pop idol
and top actor A is allegedly gay.
The boyfriend, B, is the current CEO
of his fashion platform.
Rumors say he hired him
to keep their relationship secret.
No way. That's obviously Appello.
Totes. It's Appello.
Wow, Lee Chan is gay?
- He's gay?
Hey, are A and B here referring
- to Chan and your CEO?
- What?
What?
Are they dating?
What are you talking about?
Chan is...
a heterosexual.
He once said in an interview
that an older girl at his high school
was his first love.
Then what is this?
What do you think? A blind item
circulating in the financial world.
Our company CEO and Chan?
No way.
No, impossible.
Oh, come on.
Hey, get up and eat.
Yes, this is what I'm talking about.
Wait, aren't you eating?
This is how I eat breakfast.
Hey, grabbing a drink was an excuse.
You came to eat that, right?
Bingo.
Gosh, yes. That hits the spot.
It tastes just like your mother's...
Gosh, it's so filling
to finally eat a home-cooked meal.
Can I stay at your place for a while?
No, I had to sleep on the couch,
and my back is killing me.
We could've shared the bed.
Are you insane?
I'm running late.
Eat, clean up, and go.
Hey.
Take this. You haven't even eaten.
- What's this?
- I got it from someone I work with.
It should be good.
If anything, they know good food.
Take it.
- Bye.
Clean up before you go!
CEO KANG HA-GI
Come in.
Mr. Kang, the weekly meeting
for the marketing team is ready.
- Okay. I'll be there.
- Yes, sir.
Jeez.
Hey, come and take these now.
Yes, for this lookbook shooting
we want to focus on gorpcore
as that is the trending aesthetic
at the moment.
Hobbies that are on the rise
include hiking, tennis, and running.
But the outfits
for these hobbies look too sporty.
So?
What's your point?
- Sorry?
- The key point.
The key point...
The visual concept
for the next season
is camping.
Okay, camping.
Sounds great.
From now on
please do not spend
over a minute on your presentation.
I'm not looking for
an elaborate speech,
but the actual result of your work.
Yes, sir.
Are we done here?
- Yes.
- This week
I expect everyone to go all-in
on the Appello fashion show.
It would be nice to film
what the venue is like
and upload it to our official
social media accounts.
Any volunteers?
Lastly, Mr. Kang likes
those who take the initiative.
Someone who steps up
and tries to make things happen.
I will
do it.
Other people have a lot of work to do
so I'll do it.
Yes, she has been assisting
with the management
of our social media account
so it'll help.
All right, then.
We'll go and see the rehearsal today
so be at my office by two o'clock.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Da-reum.
It's your first time on site.
Are you sure you'll be fine?
Mr. Kang.
I think I should probably go.
Let's give the volunteer a try.
That's all, then.
- Yes.
Good luck.
Mr. Kang...
Everything is so neatly organized
as expected from the office's owner.
I can't believe I spent a night here.
I want to be an outstanding employee
to join this trip.
Wait, what?
Why is he
looking at him like that?
What can I do
to show you how I feel?
I love you, Chan.
- I love you, Chan.
- "I love you, Chan"?
What can I do
to show you how I feel?
I love you...
Chan.
That blind item
must be true.
What do I do? What now?
NO IMPORTANT DOCUMENT ON THE DESK
- Did you wait long?
- Sorry?
No, I just got here.
I left the weekly meeting report
on your desk, sir.
NO LEAKAGE OF CONFIDENTIAL INFO
- Let's go.
- Sorry?
Right. Yes.
Let's go.
- These days,
- Yes?
is the job market tough?
Yes, that's the case.
Someone with your credentials
could've gone to major corporations.
Gosh, hardly.
By any chance
any special reason
why you came to Appello?
Actually, I wanted
to learn more about myself.
Instead of just getting
more qualifications
I wanted to find out
what I truly love.
That was why I chose
to come to a place I was drawn to.
Also
there was someone
I really wanted to meet.
Who is it?
What?
Did I just say it out loud?
That was why I heard it.
Well, what I meant
was that I wanted to meet many people
in different industries on the job.
Something like that.
Mr. Kang, may I ask something too?
Sure.
Why did you come to Appello?
At first,
it was because of one person.
Could that be Chan?
But now, Appello is my everything.
- What's this? A prize draw?
- It's a prize draw.
Thank you.
My gosh. So that's how it looks.
That's cool.
That is so awesome.
Is she putting on a show,
trying to look innocent?
Goodness, Mr. Kang!
I can't believe
you came all the way here yourself.
- Hello.
- Of course, I should come.
How's it coming along?
Yes, of course.
A new brand like ours
could never even dream
of having a fashion show.
Thank you very much
for giving us this great opportunity.
Don't mention it.
Your brand already had the appeal.
The opportunity simply found you.
Anyway, I've never seen those before.
This kind of event is a rare chance.
So we even took out a loan
to make lots of new products.
Although we wouldn't survive
until the next season
if they end up as inventory.
Oh, I almost jinxed it. Never mind.
I won't let that happen.
I'll make sure
people see our products
and immediately go, "It's Go.Co."
I will make it happen.
I can do it!
- Yes, please keep up the good work.
- Thanks.
See you at the show.
All right. Keep it up, Mr. Kang!
- Let's go!
- Go for it!
What are you smiling about?
I had a thought that fashion brands
and K-pop idol groups are similar.
- K-pop idol?
- Yes.
They show their presence on the stage
bring thrills to people
with their visuals
and above all, they're loved
by their fans for a very long time.
Everyone must've put in
so much hard work
just to get their chance
on that stage.
I really hope this fashion show
becomes a huge hit.
I'll put in everything I have too.
Now, let us begin!
The first model, walk up to the spot.
Maintain a three-second interval.
Now, go!
Cool.
- What happened?
- Cut.
Are you okay?
- Hey, go check on the model.
- Yes, sir.
Reduce the amount of dry ice.
- Was it because of dry ice?
- Yes, it looks like it.
If too much dry ice is used,
it creates vapors.
That's why he almost fell
on stage before.
Let's wipe the stage.
Can I have someone test the stage
before we begin?
Anyone wearing dress shoes
among the staff?
Can I do it?
These heels are pretty low.
I think these will be okay.
- Can I ask you to do it then?
- Of course.
Why would you?
If models get hurt, that will cause
problems for the show.
I'll go walk slowly.
- Do I start behind the stage?
- Yes. Thank you.
Oh, no.
Ms. Nam!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Oh, yes. I'm okay.
You should've just walked.
Why did you make a turn?
You almost hurt your head
from your carelessness.
I know. Why did I do that?
It's a bit watery over here.
Someone should wipe over here.
- Okay. Hey, go wipe it.
- Yes.
We have Lee Chan playing the role
of Seong-jun who appears
to be perfect in every way
but actually clumsy and vulnerable
when it comes to love
and Yoon Cho-yi who plays the role
of Yi-seo who matures by experiencing
the sweetest moment
as well as the most bitter breakup.
The two lead roles of Bitter Sweet.
Can you please make a heart?
Can you look to the left?
Now, to the center.
To the right, please.
Very nice.
It's time for questions.
If you have any questions,
please raise your hands
and we'll pass you the mic.
- Yes?
- Your unique chemistry was
already evident in the preview.
I wonder if you grew any feelings
for each other
while working on this film.
Well, to be honest, who wouldn't be
fluttered to see Lee Chan?
I've been a fan of his
for a long time
so that helped me focus
on portraying my emotions.
Well, Ms. Cho-yi is very lovely.
I think this drama did a good job
of showcasing her charms.
If I meet someone like her
in real life
I can't help but fall in love.
LEE CHAN AND YOON CHO-YI
GETTING FLUTTERED WHILE FILMING?
Good job today.
- Thank you.
See you later.
- Bye.
Good work, Mr. Lee.
Yes, good work.
Give me a second.
Did you receive the gift I sent you?
I gave it to my friend.
What?
You've been ignoring my calls.
How long will you keep doing this?
Cho-yi.
We broke up.
- It's time for you to accept it.
- No.
I can't break up with you.
No, I'm not breaking up with you.
I really loved you.
Are you saying you didn't love me?
Not even for a moment?
I did have feelings for you.
But it wasn't love.
But why?
What do I lack?
It's not that you lacked anything.
We just weren't right for each other.
Cho-yi.
You're perfect
just the way you are, okay?
Do you know how much I struggled
and endured to put up with you?
Are you saying
I wasn't right for you?
Do you think all that struggling
and enduring means love?
Someone who lets you be yourself.
Find someone like that.
This is ridiculous.
You pretend to be polite and sweet.
But you're just pretending
to be the better person to leave me.
...I
I won't ever break up with you.
So...
you might as well endure it.
Well, should I play some music?
Oh, yes. I'd love that.
What...
Why is this...
INCOMING CALL
LEE CHAN
ANSWER
- Hello?
- Where are you?
It's really Chan.
I'm almost at work. Where are you?
Me? Not sure.
What? We spent all night together.
But do you miss me already?
"All night"?
Hey, stop joking around, will you?
What? We were good together
until this morning.
Until this morning?
By the way,
what am I supposed to pick up?
Whatever. I'll throw it out.
You're better off without seeing it.
What can I do to show you how I feel?
I love you, Chan.
Is he throwing out that card?
The power is off.
I can't believe
Mr. Kang was in love with Chan.
How did I end up
finding out this secret?
You're still here?
Director Lee.
Have you been well?
Yes.
Oh, hello.
Who was your favorite in D.N.X?
Well...
Pardon?
How did you know that?
You're listening to our song
from ten years ago.
By any chance...
was it me?
Right?
It was.
I'm doomed.
Gosh...
How did you get that right
on your first try?
Just my gut feeling.
Oh, my gosh. That's crazy.
You must've been a fan
since you were a kid.
You can call me Chan
when it's just the two of us.
Oh, no. Still...
I will
call you Da-reum.
Is that okay with you?
Yes.
Chan.
It's been over ten years
since D.N.X disbanded.
I didn't know there was still someone
who listened to our music.
Thank you.
I've listened to it for so long
that it's become part of my routine.
When I'm walking or working
I find myself listening to it
without even realizing it.
NAM DA-REUM
- Give me your phone.
- What?
I left it in the office.
There.
Call me.
I will.
You promise?
No way.
Awesome.
Is this really Chan's number?
Yes.
Hey. Namda.
She's completely out of it.
A celeb giving you his number?
What's that supposed to mean?
He told you to call him.
Call him and find out.
I doubt he really meant it.
It's just that I work for his company
and I'm an old fan, so...
So?
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe he gave it to you
because he had a crush on you.
- What?
- She's right.
He could've saved your number
on his phone.
Why did he have to do that?
Why did he write it on your hand?
He was totally flirting.
Hey. He wasn't.
That's totally not true.
First things first.
Let's save it.
Don't do anything other than saving.
What the? Are you really calling him?
Hey. No. Stop it.
Are you nuts? Get back here.
Give it to me.
Hey.
What do I do? What am I going to say?
Hello?
Chan?
It's me, Da-reum.
Hello?
Isn't this Director Lee's number?
Director Lee?
Yes, this is his number.
I work for Director Lee's company.
Oh, my Chan?
He's in the shower.
Sorry about that.
Saying you work for him
after calling him Chan?
That's beyond ridiculous.
DELETE THIS CONTACT?
BITTER SWEET
What's the next scene?
Prepare it thoroughly...
What are you doing in my green room?
The next scene.
Will you help me rehearse?
We still need to do our job.
- Do you want to grab coffee?
- Let's get coffee.
Namda.
I told you not to call him. See?
Why did he lead you on
when he has a girlfriend?
I told you it wasn't like that.
You're the same.
Look what you've done.
I'm doomed.
Oh, I'm doomed.
- It's your fault.
- Why did you do that?
- You called him.
- Because you told me to.
But you know what
this is for the better.
If Chan answered,
it would've been really awkward.
Namda.
You're not disappointed?
Chan is human after all.
Of course, he can have a girlfriend.
I actually want him to meet someone
and be happy.
Hey. A true fan is different.
I approve.
What time is it?
Hey. It's time for Chan's drama.
It's the first episode.
Make sure you stay for it.
Hey.
What's that look on your face?
Are you out of your mind? Hey.
Who are you to be disappointed?
You've been a fan for 12 years.
Get a grip.
What if my call interrupted him?
I hope
he doesn't think I'm a crazy fan.
Oh, forget it.
I don't want to think about it.
Hold on.
I love you, Chan.
If Chan has a girlfriend...
what about Mr. Kang?
Is it one-sided?
That's pitiful.
Oh, gosh.
SUNGJU
Here's your Americano.
Thank you.
How long has he been bottling
his feelings alone?
Did he want to stay by his side
even as a friend?
Mr. Kang, have this
and cheer up.
Good luck.
Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kang. Were you looking for me?
It's been up there for too long.
I've seen it for too long,
it's not so impressive anymore.
Okay, I'll replace it
as soon as possible.
I thought you didn't drink coffee.
What's gotten into you?
Well, it's not so bad.
Good. One, two.
Good. Look at the window. One, two.
Nice.
Fix his hair, please.
Nice. One, two. Smile a bit.
One, two. Excellent.
One more. One, two.
Good job.
- I just love the photos today.
- The colors looked perfect.
- Let me get ready for the next set.
- Okay.
- Hey. Can I have my phone?
- Yes.
- Did I get any calls?
- No.
Are you expecting one?
No.
UNREAD
I just wanted to treat her to a meal.
- Who?
- Just...
Someone I'm grateful to.
Mr. Kang, please confirm the location
for the fashion show.
Sure.
Mr. Kang, do you drink coffee now?
Yes, it happened somehow.
- You may proceed.
- Thank you.
Wait...
Yes, sir.
How is Nam Da-reum doing?
In terms of work and all.
I think
she's very diligent.
She always takes initiative
and does her best in everything.
She's very cheerful.
She actually asked me
about how to become
the outstanding employee.
The outstanding employee?
Yes.
- Are the materials ready?
- Yes.
- Won-tae, let's go.
- Okay.
Da-reum, have you sorted out
the messenger promotion message
- on the Appello fashion show?
- Oh, yes.
I prepared two reminder versions
for the day of the show.
Give me one second.
MESSENGER
NO RESULTS FOUND
- What's taking so long?
- I...
The files are gone.
Gone?
Yes.
I'll make them quickly.
I've already done it once.
It won't take long.
Did you actually do it?
We're updating it tomorrow.
Make sure to send it to me by today.
I'm sorry.
Did someone touch my computer?
No, I doubt it.
I probably lost it.
APPELLO FASHION SHOW
MESSENGER MESSAGE PROPOSAL
I won't have a chance
of becoming an outstanding employee
let alone an ordinary employee.
How can he work overtime every day?
Seriously, that's amazing.
That's strange.
I swear it was on the wallpaper.
What? I'm just borrowing this.
Okay.
No.
Oh, no.
Don't overthink it.
JANGSHINCHEON, GUDORIM
INGUK STATION
Mr. Kang.
Don't you have an umbrella?
What brings you here
- I live around here.
- Really? Me too.
Let's go. I'll walk you home.
Oh, no. It's okay.
- Then will you go on your own?
- What?
No.
What happened to your car?
Why did you take the subway?
It's in the body shop.
Did you work overtime today?
Yes, a little.
If you're getting home now,
it wasn't just a little overtime.
Is there too much work to do?
Oh, no.
It's just that I made a mistake.
I bet you never make any mistakes
because you're thorough.
You're right. I don't.
But I used to make a lot of mistakes
when I was a newbie.
You make mistakes
because you're doing the job.
If you don't do anything
you won't make any mistakes.
Don't be afraid and keep trying
whether it's work
or making mistakes.
Thank you for saying that.
I was actually discouraged until now.
You're more caring than I thought.
Than you thought?
Yes, everyone is afraid of your glare
so they avoid talking to you.
Didn't you know?
What? Wait.
Anyway, this is pretty cool.
I didn't know
we lived in the same area.
How come we haven't run
into each other until now?
Bullying is the worst.
Do you know how that feels?
Maybe we have.
At a neighborhood pub.
What?
If we ever have
I bet it was
at a library or something.
Because I don't go anywhere
other than my house and the library.
I didn't know we had a bar here.
Why didn't I notice?
What happened that night...
Right. I might as well bury it.
Mr. Kang.
I'll keep your secret to my grave.
That's my house right there.
It's late. You should go home.
But we're almost there.
Why would you...
I'll walk you to your house.
No, thank you for walking me home.
You should go home. Thank you.
It's slippery.
- If you don't watch out...
- Mr. Kang!
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
EPILOGUE
This is the last train
bound for Gudorim.
Passengers for Songdam
must board this train.
SUNGJU
THIS TRAIN GUDORIM
NEXT TRAIN NONE
GUDORIM
INGUK STATION
There's no chance she'd be here.
What is this?
Our stage!
No!
Let's cheer up just a bit more.
- Is she pretty?
- Jeez.
Was she too busy to call me?
Unless our information is sent to SE
in real time
- it's hard to find out.
- Taxi.
Mr. Kang, you don't think
the spy is...
Ms. Nam.
As of this moment
you're fired.
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Songmi You
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs